http://www.libanuschurch.com/privacy-policy-notice/

You are here: Home / Privacy Policy Notice
Privacy Notice
This Privacy Notice applies to the Libanus Evangelical Church website and governs data collected from those users of this website.  By using this website, you consent to the data practices described in this Privacy Notice.
Personal Data
Libanus Church may collect personal identifiable information, such as your e-mail address, name, home or work address or telephone number by users submitting such information to this website.
Some information about your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected by Libanus Evangelical Church website, this may include your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses.  This information is used by us for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Libanus Evangelical Church Web site.
Use of Cookies
The Libanus Evangelical Church Web site uses “cookies” to help personalise your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server.
Please note that:
Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer
Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you
One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time
The main purpose of a cookie is to tell the web server that you have returned to a specific page, if you return to the same web site, the information you previously provided can be easily retrieved and you can easily reuse any features that you customised.
You have the ability to accept or decline cookies through your web browser.   Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer.
If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the services of Libanus Evangelical Church or other web sites you visit.
Storing and Using Data
Libanus Evangelical Church complies with its obligations under the “GDPR” by keeping personal data up-to-date; by storing and destroying it securely; by not collecting or retaining excessive amounts of data; by protecting personal data from loss, misuse, unauthorized access and disclosure, and by ensuring that appropriate technical measures are in place to protect personal data.
A full copy of the Libanus Evangelical Church’s Privacy Notice is available by clicking the link below.
If you are a member of the church or a regular attender or an employee of the church then the whole of this policy will apply to you.
Contact Details
To exercise all relevant rights, queries or complaints, please, in the first instance, contact Libanus Evangelical Church Administrator at Libanus Evangelical Church, Market Street, Morriston, Swansea, SA6 8DA. Or by telephoning 01792 781902.   Alternatively by Email: Libanusoffice@gmail.com or webmlibanus@gmail.com
Libanus Church Privacy Notice
PagesAbout Us
Church Calendar
Church Constitution
Church Leadership
Church Worker
Contact us
Easter Services
February 2018
Who we are We are a Bible believing church which is situated in Morriston approximately four miles from the centre of Swansea, South Wales.
We are a family orientated fellowship made up of all ages and backgrounds who meet on Sundays at 10:00am and 6:00pm.
Pages
About Us
Our History
Church Calendar
Church Constitution
Church Leadership
Church Worker
Contact us
What’s On
Latest NewsGood Friday in MorristonMarch 31, 2018 - 3:26 pmThe Good ShepherdMarch 14, 2018 - 8:54 pm‘Drive & Dine’February 21, 2018 - 12:43 pmThe best news you’ve ever heard!February 8, 2018 - 6:13 pm
Scroll to top
